Donald-John Dorren (DJ) M: 07704228372 | Email: dj@dorren.com | Website: dj.dorren.com

PERSONAL PROFILE STATEMENT:

I have recently finished my four years studying Computing Science at the University of Dundee. I enjoyed both the individual and teamwork aspects of the course and working in an agile environment. I have also gained a solid understanding of a number of coding languages such as C#, Python and Javascript, using frameworks such as React and VueJS. I have also gained knowledge of design methodologies using Figma.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Growth Partner - Remote, United Kingdom - 06/2023 to 09/2023 Intern

- Creating a membership organisation for CEOs and entrepreneurs.
- Recruiting and researching members using Beauhurst, SimilarWeb and Hubspot.
- Automating simple tasks using Python.

Machine Labs Limited - Edinburgh, United Kingdom - 06/2022 to 08/2022 Software Engineer

- Created a location report allowing users to see the location of their customers from a worldview all the way to postcode.
- Developed an SVG map system using d3-geo to display this information in multiple layers such as a choropleth map and a heatmap.
- The final goal of this project was to give users a visual representation of their sales data. Allowing users to run campaigns on very specific regions and customer segments using Machine Lab's customer mosaic groups and see these grow over time using the heatmap system.

Parsley Box Group - Edinburgh, United Kingdom - 03/2020 to 09/2020 - 05/2021 to 09/2021 Call Centre Agent

- Customer support and order processing using Django
- •Network, PC, and software support for 200+ call centre agents
- On-site server management

EDUCATION:

University Of Dundee - BSC Hons Computing Science, 2:1

Dissertation - Developed an Amazon Alexa skill in Node.js that allows users to seamlessly add data for Citizen Science projects into a DynamoDB database. This data was tagged with the user's location allowing for a D3 map visualisation on a Vue.js website.

Games Design -Developed a procedurally generated open-world sandbox in C# using Perlin noise. The game used a Finite state machine for boss battles and general enemy AI.

Personal Projects:

Plant Monitor - Helping me keep my plants alive. Using a Raspberry Pi to monitor the plant's soil moisture content and notify me if moisture is too low using Twilio and Python.

Car Park Monitor - Using computing vision to check the number of available car spaces in the car park next to my flat.